<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Toolbox</string>
    <string name="add_activity_label">TimeTable</string>

    <string name="subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="comment">Comment</string>
    <string name="timeBegin">Time</string>
    <string name="duration">duration</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="confirm">confirm</string>
    <string name="warning_subject">subject should be more than 3 char</string>
    <string name="warning_time">specify the beginning time</string>
    <string name="warning_duration">specify duration</string>

    <!-- ViewPager -->
    <string name="tab_text_1">Table</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Weather</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Gallery</string>

    <!-- weather info -->
    <string name="weather_info">Weather Info</string>
    <string name="name_txt">name:</string>
    <string name="temp">temp:</string>
    <string name="min_temp">min temp:</string>
    <string name="max_temp">max temp:</string>
    <string name="description">description:</string>
    <string name="humidity">humidity:</string>
    <string name="pressure">pressure:</string>

    <!-- AuthorPageActivity -->
    <string name="title_activity_author_page">AuthorPageActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="developer" translatable="false">Developed By Mohammad Mahdi Salmani</string>
    <string name="share_btn">share_btn</string>
    <string name="web_page_btn" translatable="false">web_page_btn</string>
    <string name="choose_all">all</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="user_background">user_background</string>
    <string name="zero_time" translatable="false">00 : 00</string>
    <string name="duration_zero" translatable="false">0 min</string>
</resources>
